superfish.com 2013-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Superfish Visual Search Technology

This privacy policy describes our current practices for the gathering and use of information from visitors to our own web site and the WindowShopper browser add-on. If Superfish, Inc–referenced herein as “Superfish,”–decides to change the privacy policy, Superfish will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places Superfish deems appropriate so that you are aware of what information Superfish collects, how Superfish uses it, and under which circumstances, if any, Superfish may disclose it. Superfish reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

###### Your Acceptance

By using our services you signify your agreement to the privacy polices described herein. If you do not agree with our privacy policies, please do not use our services.

###### Information Collected and Stored by Superfish

Superfish may collect and store certain information that is automatically collected by WindowShopper, such as IP address, browser cookies, the url of the page you are on, download date and any other anonymous information relating to your search and any visit that you may make to a third party website as a result of the Services . In addition, Superfish will collect and store certain information that is provided by its users, such as, email address, name and address, and paypal details. Such information will be kept private by Superfish and is not for public distribution. Superfish will also store bugs hunting information provided regarding the service. This information is for Superfish’s internal use only and will not be distributed under any circumstances. Personal information may be used in several ways:

  * To enable us to respond to you or to process, validate, and verify service requests and to perform the requested services;
  * To give our own web site/service designers information useful for developing new features and services that meet our registrants’ needs;
  * To operate and improve the services;
  * To reply to customer support e-mails and to facilitate future customer support;
  * To provide a customize user experience based on the Country you are in;
  * To determine validity of the registered user;
  * To be disclosed to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, sale of assets or other corporate change of Superfish;
  * We may use anonymous data for a number of purposes such as analyzing the use of our Services and we may disclose this information to third parties. Any data shared shall be anonymous, and not contain user specific information.

###### No Sharing of Information

Except as may be stated expressly in this Privacy Policy , Superfish will not share personal information that you give us with any third party.

###### Non-Personal Information

Superfish may share non-personally identifying information (“NPII”) (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for our site and service. In such a case Superfish only uses such data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure to improve our site and service, and not in a manner that would identify you personally.

###### Disclosures Required By Law

Without derogating from the above there are a limited number of situations requiring us to disclose your personal information to others without first receiving your consent: (1) when ordered to do so by a subpoena or court order; (2) if you violate or breach an agreement with us; (3) if Superfish believes conduct by you will harm the property or rights of Superfish; (4) under exigent circumstances to protect the physical safety of Superfish its employees, users, or the general public.

###### Security Information

Our site/service has physical, electronic, and managerial security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Superfish takes many measures to protect this information while it is stored:

  * monitor system and application activity logs to identify any unusual activity, from authorized or unauthorized individuals accessing our systems or making changes to stored information. Superfish regularly perform preventative system maintenance and monitoring to ensure the security of our data systems.
  * employees sign confidentiality agreements and only our employees who need information to perform their job and who have passed background checks are granted access to personally identifiable information or any other confidential data.
  * Servers are divided such that critical machines, such as data storage, are not exposed to the web.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Superfish strive to protect your personal information, Superfish cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk. Once Superfish receive your transmission, Superfish makes its best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

###### Third Party Links

Superfish is not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or as a result of the Services nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site, any ad and/or any results provided by our Services which link you to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. We encourage you to read carefully the rules and policies of the Web sites linked to or from our Web sites or as a result of the Services before proceeding with your use or interaction on such Web site. Should you have any questions concerning such publishers, partners or third parties’ use of your information you should contact them directly.

###### Governing Terms

If you choose to use Superfish’s sites and services your use and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including as regards limitations of liability and dispute resolution.

###### Corrections and Questions

If you would like to access the personal information to correct, update or delete it, if you have any question or concern about the privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our site/Services, or any other questions about this Privacy Policy, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the “Contact Us” link on our site or sending an email to: info@superfish.com.
